Susan Clark papers
UCLA Library Special Collections
Susan Clark papers
1965-1993
2258
UCLA Library Special Collections
4.8 linear ft. (12 boxes)
Susan Clark was a motion picture and television actress. She may be best known for her role as Katherine on the television series Webster. The bulk of the collection consists of scripts from the television series Webster. Additionally there are scripts representing her work on television movies such as The Dark Tower (released as Night Moves) and Skullduggery as well guest appearances on popular television series such as Columbo and Marcus Welby, M.D.
Provenance/Source of Acquisition
Gift of Susan Clark, 2014.
Restrictions on Access
COLLECTION STORED OFF-SITE AT SRLF: Open for research. Advance notice required for access. Contact the UCLA Library Special Collections Reference Desk for paging information.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 7680423
Biography/History
Nora Golding, later changed to Susan Clark, was born March 8, 1944, in Sarnia, Ontario, Canada. Clark made her motion picture debut in the film Banning (1967) and also acted in feature films such as Madigan (1968), Coogan’s Bluff (1968), and Sherlock Holmes (1981). Clark also acted on television, appearing on Universal television-produced series such as Marcus Welby, M.D., Columbo, and The Bold Ones. From 1983-1988, Clark and her husband Alex Karras were featured in the television series, Webster. Her television movie credits include Babe (1975) for which she was awarded an Emmy for her role as Babe Didrickson Zaharias, Emelia Earhart (1976) for which she earned an Emmy nomination, Jimmy B. and Andre (1980), Maid in America (1982), Tonya and Nancy: The Inside Story (1994) and Butterbox Babies (1996). In addition to acting, Clark also produced films and founded the production company Georgian Bay Ltd. with her husband Alex Karras.
Scope and Content
The collection consists of materials related to the career of actress Susan Clark. The bulk of the materials are scripts from television series Webster. Also included are scripts from the television movies The Bold Ones, Word of Honor, and Jimmy B. and Andre, and television series guest appearances on shows such as Columbo and Marcus Welby, M.D., including others. Additionally there are scripts representing motion picture projects such as The Dark Tower (released as Night Moves) and Skullduggery, among others, and a radio script for To Damascus. Some scripts in the collection are annotated. Notably absent from the collection are material representing Clark’s involvement in the Emmy winning television movie Babe and Emmy nominated television movie Amelia Earhart.
Organization and Arrangement
The collection is arranged in the following series:
Television projects
Motion pictures projects
Radio projects.
Clark, Susan, 1940- -- Archives
Container List
- Television Projects.
  Scope and Content
  The bulk of the series consists of scripts from the television series, Webster. Additionally there are scripts representing Clark’s work on a variety of television movies such as Jimmy B. and Andre and Word of Honor, and guest appearances on television series including Columbo and Marcus Welby, M.D., among others. Some of the scripts are annotated. The series is arranged alphabetically by project title.
  - Susan Clark and Alex Karras At home Video Library - listings of videos for news media., undated. (Box 10)
  - The Astronaut - script., 1971 Nov 11. (Box 1)
  - The Big Prize - teleplay., 1967 Dec 1. (Box 1)
  - The Bold Ones: An Inalienable Right to Die - script., 1972 Sep 5. (Box 1)
  - The Bold Ones: The Lawyers, In Defense of Ellen McKay - teleplay., 1971 Sept 24. (Box 1)
  - Columbo: Lady in Waiting - script., 1971 June. (Box 1)
  - Hollywood Television Theatre: Double Solitaire - script., 1973 Feb 20. (Box 1)
    Annotated.
  - Festival - scripts., circa 1965. (Box 12)
  - The Jim and Jennifer Stolpa Story - script., 1993 Sept. (Box 10)
  - Jimmy B. and Andre - screenplay., 1979 Apr 6. (Box 11)
  - Jimmy B. and Andre - screenplay., 1979 June. (Box 11)
  - Maid in America - screenplay., 1981 Aug 31. (Box 1)
  - Marcus Welby, MD: Hello Goodbye Hello - teleplay., 1969 May 15. (Box 1)
  - Marcus Welby, MD: Please Don't Send Flowers - script., 1972 Aug 11. (Box 1)
  - The Salesman - script., 1966 May 8. (Box 12)
  - Scent - script., undated. (Box 1)
  - Something for a Lonely Man - script., 1967 June 12. (Box 1)
  - Run for Your Life: Aftermath - script., 1967 Aug 29. (Box 1)
  - Run for Your Life: Collision - script., 1967 Aug 29. (Box 2)
  - Webster: The A++ Parents - final draft., 1987 Feb 12. (Box 7)
  - Webster: Another Ballgame - sixth revised draft script., 1983 Mar 25. (Box 2)
  - Webster: And the Baby Makes Breakfast - final draft script., 1985 Aug 15. (Box 4)
  - Webster: Alien - final draft script., 1985 Sep 18. (Box 4)
  - Webster: Basketball Blues - table draft., 1988 Jan 18. (Box 9)
  - Webster: The Best Think I Can Be - final draft script., 1985 Mar 20. (Box 4)
  - Webster: Big Problems - final draft script., 1985 Sep 11. (Box 4)
  - Webster: The Big Sleepover - final draft script., 1986 Aug 21. (Box 6)
  - Webster: Borrowed Time - final draft script., 1986 Jan 9. (Box 5)
  - Webster: Bowled Over - taping script., 1988 Oct 27. (Box 9)
  - Webster: Breaking Away - final draft script., 1987 Oct 6. (Box 8)
  - Webster: Burn Out - final draft script., 1984 Aug 30. (Box 3)
  - Webster: A Camping We Will Go - taping script., 1988 Dec 1. (Box 10)
  - Webster: Chained - final draft script., 1985 Nov 14. (Box 5)
  - Webster: The Chelsea Cat - taping script., 1988 Sep 29. (Box 9)
  - Webster: The Crush - taping script., 1988 Apr 21. (Box 9)
  - Webster: Cuckoo's Nest - final draft script., 1986 Mar 20. (Box 6)
  - Webster: The Cruise - taping script., 1987 Dec 11. (Box 8)
  - Webster: The Derby - final draft script., 1986 Aug 7. (Box 6)
  - Webster: Dial K for Katherine - taping script., 1988 Jan 7. (Box 8)
  - Webster: Doing Time at the Community Center - taping script., 1988 Sep 22. (Box 9)
  - Webster: Don't Jump, George! - third revised third draft script., 1983 Oct 6. (Box 2)
  - Webster: Educating Katherine - final draft script., 1983 Nov 1. (Box 2)
  - Webster: Farewell to Arms - final draft script., 1986 Feb 13. (Box 5)
  - Webster: Flood of Memories: The Final Chapter - taping script., 1989 Jan 20.
  - Webster: Flood of Memories: The Final Chapter., 1989 Jan 20. (Box 10)
  - Webster: The Four Tops - The Sequel - final draft script., 1987 Nov 5. (Box 8)
    The cover is signed by members of The Four Tops and the cast.
  - Webster: Freedom of the Press - taping script., 1987 Jan 8. (Box 7)
  - Webster: A Friend In Need - final draft script., 1986 Jan 23. (Box 5)
  - Webster: Games People Play - taping script., 1987 Jan 15. (Box 7)
  - Webster: George The Patient Inside of Himself - final draft script., 1983 Dec 8. (Box 2)
  - Webster: George's Brush with Life - taping draft., 1987 Sept 17. (Box 8)
  - Webster: God Bless the Child - final draft script., 1984 Sep 20. (Box 3)
  - Webster: Good Grief - final draft script., 1985 Oct 10. (Box 5)
  - Webster: Gotcha - final draft script., 1986 Feb 27. (Box 6)
  - Webster: Grab Bag - final draft script., 1987 Aug 27. (Box 8)
  - Webster: Great Expectations Part 1 - final draft script., 1985 Oct 17. (Box 5)
  - Webster: Great Expectations Part 2 - first draft script., 1985 Oct 14. (Box 5)
  - Webster: The Great Walnutto - final draft script., 1984 Aug 16. (Box 3)
  - Webster: Green-Eyed Monster - second revised first draft script., 1983 Sep 24. (Box 2)
  - Webster: Happy Un-Birthday - final draft script., 1983 July 25. (Box 2)
  - Webster: A Hell of a Weekend - taping script., 1987 Oct 15. (Box 8)
  - Webster: Hello, I Must Be Going - final draft script., 1985 Dec 12. (Box 5)
  - Webster: Hello, Nicky - revised first draft script., 1987 Aug 18. (Box 8)
  - Webster: Here comes the Jets - taping script., 1988 Nov 17. (Box 10)
  - Webster: Honor Thy Grandfather - taping script., 1986 Dec 11. (Box 7)
  - Webster: How the West Once Was - final draft script., 1985 July 25. (Box 4)
  - Webster: The Importance of Being Worthy - taping script., 1987 Sep 24. (Box 8)
  - Webster: In the Family Way, Part I - final draft script., 1985 Jan 10. (Box 4)
  - Webster: In the Family Way, Part II - final draft script., 1985 Jan 17. (Box 4)
  - Webster: In Re: Webster Long, Part II - final draft script., 1984 July 12. (Box 3)
  - Webster: In Re: Webster Long, Part III - final draft script., 1984 July 19. (Box 3)
  - Webster: It's a Dog's Life - final draft script., 1984 Nov 15. (Box 3)
  - Webster: Katherine Fights City Hall - final draft script., 1984 Sep 13. (Box 3)
  - Webster: Katherine the Brave - taping script., 1987 Jan 22. (Box 7)
  - Webster: Katherine, the Greek - taping draft script., 1987 Oct 22. (Box 8)
  - Webster: Katherine's Swan Song - revised first draft script., 1983 Jul 26. (Box 2)
  - Webster: Keep on Truckin', Papa - final draft script., 1984 Dec 20. (Box 4)
  - Webster: Kiss Me Kate - taping script., 1986 Oct 2. (Box 6)
  - Webster: Knock, Knock - final draft script., 1984 Aug 23. (Box 3)
  - Webster: The K.O. Kid - taping script., 1986 Dec 4. (Box 7)
  - Webster: The Landlords - final draft script., 1986 July 31. (Box 6)
  - Webster: Leave it to Diva - taping script., 1986 Dec 18. (Box 7)
  - Webster: Love Papadopolis Style - final draft script., 1986 Jan 16. (Box 5)
  - Webster: Maybe Baby - first draft script., 1983 Dec 12. (Box 3)
  - Webster: The Man in the Red Flannel Suit - taping script., 1986 Nov 13. (Box 7)
  - Webster: McGruff - final draft script., 1986 July 24. (Box 6)
  - Webster: Moving On - final draft script., 1984 Sep 27. (Box 3)
  - Webster: My Family's Honor - final draft script., 1986 Mar 26. (Box 6)
  - Webster: One More Shot - revised first draft script., 1985 Sep 4. (Box 4)
  - Webster: Our Song - taping script., 1987 Feb 5. (Box 7)
  - Webster: The Painting - taping script., 1988 Apr 7. (Box 9)
  - Webster: Papa's Big Romance - taping script., 1988 Mar 17. (Box 9)
  - Webster: Parent Trap - final draft script., 1985 Sep 26. (Box 5)
  - Webster: Parental Guidance Suggested - taping script., 1988 Feb 18. (Box 9)
  - Webster: Playball - taping script., 1986 Oct 15. (Box 7)
  - Webster: Please Pass the Potatoes, Obie or Thanksgiving with the Four Tops - taping script., 1988 Nov 10. (Box 9)
  - Webster: A Question of Honor - first draft script., 1983 Oct 10. (Box 2)
  - Webster: Read It and Weep - final draft script., 1986 Aug 28. (Box 6)
  - Webster: Rich Man, Poor Man - taping script., 1988 May 26. (Box 9)
  - Webster: Rub-a-Dub-Dub - Taping Script., 1988 March 3. (Box 9)
  - Webster: A Run for the Money - taping script., 1986 Sep 17. (Box 6)
  - Webster: Runaway - final draft script., 1984 Dec 6. (Box 4)
  - Webster: Sale Away - taping script., 1988 Apr 14. (Box 9)
  - Webster: San Francisco, Parts I, II, and III - final draft script., 1987 Jul 28. (Box 8)
  - Webster: Saying Goodbye - revised first draft script., 1983 Aug 27. (Box 2)
  - Webster: Second Time Around - first draft script., 1983 Sep 12. (Box 2)
  - Webster: Secrets - taping script., 1986 Nov 20. (Box 7)
  - Webster: See George Run - taping script. (Box 9)
  - Webster: Selling It Through - taping script., 1986 Sep 4. (Box 6)
  - Webster: Simple Gifts - revised table draft script., 1987 Nov 9. (Box 8)
  - Webster: Simple Gifts - taping script., 1987 Nov 12. (Box 8)
  - Webster: Special Delivery - final draft script., 1986 March 13. (Box 6)
  - Webster: Strike Up the Band - final draft script., 1984 Dec 13. (Box 4)
  - Webster: Take My Cousin... Please - revised table draft script., 1988 Sep 9. (Box 9)
  - Webster: Taming of the Stew - taping script., 1987 Dec 3. (Box 8)
  - Webster: Teddy Bear Scare - first draft script., 1983 Nov 3. (Box 2)
  - Webster: A Test of Characters - taping script., 1986 Oct 30. (Box 7)
  - Webster: Thanksgiving Show - final draft script., 1984 Oct 4. (Box 3)
  - Webster: That's Entertainment - final draft script., 1983 Oct 24. (Box 2)
  - Webster: That's Rich - final draft script., 1985 Dec 5. (Box 5)
  - Webster: There Goes the Bride - final draft script., 1986 Feb 20. (Box 6)
  - Webster: They Don't Shoot Horses, Do They? - taping script., 1989 Jan 5. (Box 10)
  - Webster: Ticket to Ride - taping script., 1988 Dec 8. (Boxes 10)
  - Webster: To Tell the Truth - final draft script., 1984 Nov 29. (Box 4)
  - Webster: Too Much Class - final draft script., 1984 Nov 8. (Box 3)
  - Webster: Trans - first draft script., 1983 Aug 19. (Box 2)
  - Webster: The Triangle - final draft script., 1985 Aug 21. (Box 4)
  - Webster: The Tribute - taping script., 1986 Oct 23. (Box 7)
  - Webster: The Truth Hurts - final draft script., 1985 Nov 21. (Box 5)
  - Webster: TV or Not TV - final draft script., 1985 Dec 19. (Box 5)
  - Webster: Uh-oh Feeling - final draft script., 1984 Oct 25. (Box 3)
  - Webster: What is Art? - final draft script., 1985 Jan 24. (Box 4)
  - Webster: What Price Friendship - 100th taping script., 1987 Feb 19. (Box 8)
  - Webster: Who's to Blame - final draft script., 1985 Oct 31. (Box 5)
  - Webster: The Wild, Wild, Webst - taping script., 1988 May 2. (Box 9)
  - Webster: Witchbusters - taping script., 1986 Sep 25. (Box 6)
  - Webster: You Can't Go Home Again - final draft script., 1984 Nov 1. (Box 3)
  - Webster: Correspondence from Hoffman Estates Police Department., 1985 Feb 1. (Box 10)
  - Webster: Holiday Mailing Lists., 1986-1988. (Box 10)
  - Webster: Kidstuff ephemera., 1985 Sep 10. (Box 10)
  - Webster: Postcards., undated. (Box 10)
  - Webster: Publicity Photograph., undated. (Box 10)
  - Webster: Shooting Schedules., 1984-1988. (Box 10)
  - Word of Honor - script., 1980 Jan 4. (Box 12)
  - Word of Honor - script., 1980 Sep. (Box 12)
  - Untitled script., undated. (Box 12)
- Motion Picture Projects.
  The series consists of motion picture scripts in which Susan Clark was involved. Included are scripts repesenting The Dark Tower (released as Night Moves) and Skullduggery, among others. A number of the scripts are annotated. The series is arranged alphabetically by scripts title.
  - Barometer Rising - script., undated. (Box 10)
    With holograph notes. Some pages have annotations on markers between the pages or on the backs of script pages.
  - The Dark Tower - script (released as Night Moves)., 1973 Sept 17. (Box 10)
  - Deirdre - screenplay., 1972 March. (Box 10)
  - The Midnight Man - script., 1973. (Box 11)
  - Out at the Country Club - screenplay., 1966 Aug 29. (Box 11)
  - Personal Maid - script., undated. (Box 12)
    Post-it on cover annotated: File copy first draft.
  - Showdown - screenplay., 1972 Apr 3. (Box 11)
  - Skin Game - script., 1971 Jan 13. (Box 11)
  - Skullduggery - screenplay., 1968 Oct 4. (Box 11)
- Radio Projects.
  This series contains one annotated script representing the project, To Damascus.
  - To Damascus - script., undated. (Box 12)